eurodns.com 2018-07-25

# 

We may collect other data that you submit via our social media accounts as well as other means of communication. For example, we may collect personal data when you provide feedback or when you participate in interactive features such as surveys, contests, or promotions.  

In case you subscribe to our newsletter, certain personal data may be transferred to our partner, The Rocket Science Group, LLC 675 Ponce de Leon Ave NE, Suite 5000, Atlanta, GA 30308, USA, who is operating MailChimp, the service we use to manage the sending of our newsletter. While they don’t have access to your data, it is nonetheless hosted on their platform.

 ** _Type of data_**  
Email address, first and last name, postal address, language preference, your login, your IP address. __ ** _Basis and Purpose_**  
We only collect and process this data for the provision of our service. __ ** _Retention_**  
We keep your personal data for as long as you hold an account with EuroDNS. Should you want to close your account, please contact support@eurodns.com and we will anonymise all personal data attached to your account. However, please be aware that in certain cases regulatory or legal obligations may prevent EuroDNS from completely deleting your personal data. For example, we are required to keep every invoice we issue for ten (10) years.

We collect certain payment and billing information when you order paid services. For example, we ask you to designate a billing contact, including name and contact information. You might also provide payment information, such as payment card details or PayPal identifiers.

 ** _Type of data_**  
Partial credit card information including first and last name, and PayPal account identifier. ~~~~ ** _Basis and Purpose_**  
We only collect and process this data for the provision of our service. __ ** _Retention_**  
We keep your personal data for as long as you hold an account with EuroDNS. Should you want to close your account, please contact [support@eurodns.com](mailto:support@eurodns.com) and we will anonymise all personal data attached to your account. However, please be aware that in certain cases regulatory or legal obligations may prevent EuroDNS from completely deleting your personal data. For example, we are required to keep every invoice we issue for ten (10) years.  

 ** _Type of data_**  
Any data provided by you when submitting a request for support. __ ** _Basis and Purpose_**  
We only collect and process this data for the provision of our service. **** ** _Retention_** ~~~~  
We keep your personal data for as long as you hold an account with EuroDNS. Should you want to close your account, please contact[support@eurodns.com](mailto:support@eurodns.com) and we will anonymise all personal data attached to your account. However, please be aware that in certain cases regulatory or legal obligations may prevent EuroDNS from completely deleting your personal data.   

For this service, you will be required to provide additional personal data by creating contact profiles which will be transferred to each registry with whom you want to register a domain name. Additionally, in case you have selected a so-called generic extension, a copy of your contact profiles will also be stored with Iron Mountain Intellectual Property Management, Inc. 9210 Sky Park Court, Suite 220 San Diego, CA 92123 USA, which is the ICANN-authorised escrow service provider that we use. Although established in the United States, this company adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.

 ** _Type of data_**  
First and last name, postal address, email address, phone number. __ ** _Basis and Purpose_**  
Collection and processing of this data is necessary to comply with our legal obligations as data processor for registries. Transfer of relevant data is a mandatory requirement by the registries who have a monopoly on the extensions they manage. __ _ **Retention**_  
Each registry has its own retention period but in general this does not exceed two years after the deletion of the Domain Name. For further information, please refer to the applicable registry policy: [https://www.eurodns.com/regist...](https://www.eurodns.com/registries-policies) _ ~~~~ ****_ _ **Transfer Abroad**_ ~~~~  
Depending on the registry you would like to register a domain name with, your personal data may be transferred outside the EEA.  

For the provision of this service, we will share some of your personal data with the certification authority GMO GlobalSign Ltd Springfield House, Sandling Road, Maidstone, Kent, ME14 2LP, United Kingdom.

For the provision of this service, we will share some of your personal data with CHIP S.A. 21, rue Léon Laval L-3372 Leudelange, Luxembourg, the TMCH service provider.

Unless your request is deemed excessive or unfounded, you may exercise the following rights in relation to your personal data:  

 ** _1\. Right of access_**  

You have the right to request a copy of the personal data that we hold about you. You may do so via your EuroDNS account [https://my.eurodns.com/account/preferences#](http://my.eurodns.com/account/preferences#) or, alternatively, request it at [support@eurodns.com](mailto:support@eurodns.com). 

**_  2\. Right of rectification _**

You have a right to correct data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete. You may do so via your EuroDNS account [https://my.eurodns.com/account/preferences#](http://my.eurodns.com/account/preferences#) or, alternatively, request it at [support@eurodns.com](mailto:support@eurodns.com).  _ **  
**_

 _ **  3\. Right to be forgotten **_

In certain circumstances, you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records. Please contact [support@eurodns.com](mailto:support@eurodns.com) and we will anonymise all personal data attached to your account. However, please be aware that in certain cases regulatory or legal obligations may prevent EuroDNS from completely deleting your personal data.

 ** _  4\. Right of portability _**

You have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organisation. You may export your data via your EuroDNS account [https://my.eurodns.com/account/preferences#](http://my.eurodns.com/account/preferences#) or, alternatively, request it at [support@eurodns.com](mailto:support@eurodns.com).

 ** _  5\. Right to object_**

You have the right to object to certain types of processing of your personal data such as direct marketing. To do so please contact our legal department at [legal@eurodns.com](mailto:legal@eurodns.com). 

Lastly, you have the right to file a complaint with the Luxembourgish Data Protection Authority, when you are of the opinion that our processing of your personal data is not in compliance with applicable legislation. Their complaint form is accessible at: [https://cnpd.public.lu/fr/particuliers/faire-valoir/formulaire-plainte.html](https://cnpd.public.lu/fr/droits/faire-valoir/formulaire-plainte.html)
